Guide to the John Noble papers, 1957-2016.
Noble, John papers,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
John Noble papers, 1957-2016.
7850
John. Noble
4 cubic feet.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, invitations, fliers, forms, photocopies of news articles, serials, and newsletters related to multiple LGBT organizations in the Rochester, NY area.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Gay activist and politician in Rochester, NY.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, invitations, fliers, forms, photocopies of news articles, serials, and newsletters related to multiple LGBT organizations in the Rochester, NY area.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Noble, John.
Subjects:
Gay activists.; Gay men -- Societies and clubs -- Rochester.; Lesbians -- Societies and clubs -- Rochester.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Related collection: Gay Alliance Of The Genesee Valley Records, #7560.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Dignity Materials
Series II. Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley
Series III. New York State Lesbian and Gay Lobby
Series IV. Rochester Gay Task Force
Series V. Rochester Lesbian and Political Caucus
Series VI. Newsletters
Series VII. Shoulders to Stand On (STSO)
Series VIII. Empire Bears
Series IX. Empire State Pride Agenda
Series X. Miscellaneous
Series XI. Political
CONTAINER LIST
- Dignity Materials, 1977, 1981-1983
  - Blank page on Dignity Letterhead, Date Unknown (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dignity, Inc. membership as reported, 1981-06-30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Executive House of Delegates Meeting, 1981-09-03-1981-09-04 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Letter to friend regarding Statement of Support for Human and Civil Rights for Homosexual Persons from John O. Noble, marked up (2), Date Unknown (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Position Description for Roman Catholic Priest Chaplain (2)(notes on reverse), Date Unknown (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Proposed standing rules, meeting of the Executive House of Delegates, Date Unknown (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agenda for Mid-Atlantic Regional Conference, 1977-08-28 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dignity Resolutions, 1977-08-13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dignity Magazine, 1977-06-1981-09 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dignity Convention Information, 1977-07 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Financial Report, 1977-07 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Folders with Dignity Inc. materials, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Insight newsletters vol 1, no. 4; vol. 2, no. 1, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - International Constitution for Dignity, Date Unknown (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - List of addresses, Date Unknown (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - List of workshops at the Convention, 1977-09-02 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Membership Report, 1977-08-15 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of Business Meeting, 1981-05-03 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Personal Schedule Book for Dignity/International Third Biennial Convention, 1977-09-02 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Press release on Fr. McNeill, 1977-09-03 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Program for Dignity/International Third Biennial Convention, 1977-09-02 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Statement of Position and Purpose, Date Unknown (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Women’s Survey, 1977-06 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Letters, 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statement, 1977-06-30 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Letters, 1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley, 1977-2010
  - Board Meeting Agenda, 1990-12-12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1990-11-14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Calendar of events, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Financial Report, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Letters to John Noble, 1977-2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Request for funds/volunteers, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Balance Sheet, 1985-12-31 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board Meeting handwritten notes, 1986-04-09 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1985-12-11 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1986-01-08 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1986-03-12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors Annual Meeting, 1985-04-07 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1977-07-12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Brochures for GAGV, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Budget, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Documentary Heritage Program Grant Program, Midterm Report, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Flier call for LGBT records, Documentary Heritage Program, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - GAGV Newsletter, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Income and Expense Report for February issue of the Empty Closet, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - President's Report, 1986-03-12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer’s Report, 1986-01-31 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Letters, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Community Outreach for STSO Budget Proposal, 2008-07-11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Documentation Project Narrative Grant Application and Narrative, Winter (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Report, 1992-11-09 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Annual Financial Report, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Annual Report, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Board Meeting Agenda, 1990-07-11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Board Meeting Agenda, 1992-11-11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Board Meeting Minutes, 1990-06-13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Board Meeting Minutes, 1991-12-11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Board Meeting Minutes, 1992-05-13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Board Meeting Minutes, 1993-01-13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Board Meeting Minutes, 1993-05-12 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Board Members, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Consolidated Balance Sheet, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1990-07-08 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Fundraising Committee Minutes, 1990-07-05 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GAGV Highlights, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gay Alliance General Ledger Income Statement, 1990-05-31 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - History of the GLBT Community of Genesee Valley, Outline (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Letters, 1990-2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Packet regarding DHP Grant Application and project, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Budget Summary, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rochester Roots: A Chronology, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Shoulders to Stand On Material, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Slides, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Video History Project Agenda, GAGV Youth Center, 2008-04-18-2008-08-08 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- New York State Lesbian and Gay Lobby, 1985-1988
  - Agenda, 1988-08-20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Financial Update, 1988-06-23-1988-08-20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Update, 1988-08-20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Year Activities, 1988-08-20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Big Brother Big Sister Proposal, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Brochure for NYSLGL, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Contact form for Lobby Day, Appointments with Legislators, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Fliers, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - New York State Assembly vote list, A2480-A, 1985-05-09 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - New York State Assembly vote list, A7045, 1985-06-25 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - State of New York Assembly #7045, 1985-03-26 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - General Fund Financial Update, 1986-04-01-1986-06-10 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - General Fund Financial Update, 1985-12-04-1986-01-31 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letters, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lobbyist Fund, Financial Update, 1986-04-01-1986-06-10 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lobbyist Fund, Financial Update, 1985-12-04-1986-01-31 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lobbyist’s Report, 1986-02-01 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Agenda, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Memorandum re 1986 Gay/Lesbian Lobby Day, Albany, 1986-05-06 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Proposed Agenda, 1986-04-05 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letter regarding Bill #1307 with attached note, 1987-02-21 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - NYSLGL General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1986-12-13 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - NYSLGL General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1987-04-04 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Rochester Gay Task Force, 1977
  - City Council Candidates Poll, 1977 (3), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Flier for the Monroe County Human Relations Commission, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Form for contribution for National Gay Task Force, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Letter to Michael Robertson regarding Human Rights Municipal Code, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Monroe County Legislature Candidates Poll, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Brochure for Rochester Gay Task Force, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Copied articles, 1977-06 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Information on Rochester Task Force on Gay Liberation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Letter to Genesee Valley Clergy regarding support, 1977-06-18 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Rochester Lesbian and Political Caucus, 1981-1985
  - Form for Candidate with issues of school board, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Letters to Congressman Barber, 1983-03-25-1983-05-04 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Letters to Governor Mario Cuomo, 1983-05-10-1983-06-30 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Letters to James Ide, 1983-04-18-1983-05-12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Other Letters, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Questionnaire for candidates, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Newsletters, 1977-2009
  - Insight newsletter vol. 4 no. 3, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Action Allert, 1990-11 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Battering Ram, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Capital District Gay Report vol. 2 no. 2, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Commonweal, Volume CIV, no.19, 1977-09-16 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Empire Garden vol. 1 no. 3, 1981-05 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Gay Chicago, Issue Number 12, 1977-08 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Hillside Campgrounds, 1990 (with event list), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Hillside Campgrounds, 2000 (with event list), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Boletin D’Nosotros, Year 2, No. 5, 1992-02 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - G.L.O.B.E. Newsletter, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Gay Light, 1977-07-07 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Oneida Rag, Vol. 3, Issue 1, 2008-04-18 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Oneida Rag, Vol. 4, No. 23, 2009-09-19 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - The Pink Paper, Vol. 7, No. 5, 1996-02 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Shoulders to Stand On (STSO), 1985, 2014-2017
  - STSO general information, 2017-02-03 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - STSO Meeting Agenda and Materials, 2016-01-15 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - STSO Documentary related with various drafts, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Educational Guide Meeting Minutes, 2014-10-22-2015-05-20 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Educational Guide Meeting Agenda, 2014-10-29-2015-06-03 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - NEH Grant drafts and working material, 2014-12-18-2016-06-23 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Articles AIDS, 1985-08 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Empire Bears, 2006-2009
  - Brew City Bears Club Information, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Email regarding April Meeting Minutes, 2009-05-06 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Empire Bears General Membership Meeting, 2009-05-06 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Empire Bears Treasurer’s Report, 2009-05 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Flier for Empire Bears St. Patrick’s Day, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Information on Empire Bears includes minutes and articles (pages are cut-off), Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Invoice for American Products, 2006-07-11 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Lone Star Bears home page, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Party Ad, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Treasurer’s Report, 2009-05-06 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Empire State Pride Agenda, 1976-2010
  - Letter regarding support, 1991-04-22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Letter regarding support, 1997-05-27 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Letter to John Noble regarding fundraiser, 1991-05-21 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Letter to John Noble regarding support, 2009-05-28 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Monthly Report to Major Donors, 1991-05 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Invitations and Fliers, 1987-2010 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Personal, 1981-2008 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Brochure: Fr. McNeill Speaks Moral Theology as a News Event, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Letter to Dignity Board of Consultors regarding donations, 1977-03-26 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Letter to Kevin Scahill regarding Dignity/Rochester, 1976-02-27 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Newsletter for Community Church of New York, Unitarian Universalist, 1983-03-20 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - God and Gays: A New Team?, 1976-10 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Projected Dignity/Integrity Budget, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Battering Ram Newsletter and Brochure, 1991-2008-09 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous, 1975-2016
  - “An urgent message to Prime Minister Trudeau.” Toronto Star, 1981-02-14 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - “Police action in march shocks lawyers’ head.”, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - “SDS, 1967-1968”, Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Brooklyn Diocesan Paper, Letter to readers of the Tablet, 1981-04-11 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Corporate Influence on Political Policy Bibliography, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Empire Bears Budget, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Empire Bears Business card for John Noble, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Form for Second Annual 2003 EBZ Awards, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Green Thursday Tape Inventory, donated to GAGV Archives, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Handwritten note from Bill, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Handwritten note on Justin Feasel, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Helping people with AIDS, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - List of gay bars, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - New York Council for the Humanities: 2016 Grant Guidelines, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - New York State Lesbian and Gay Lobby Minutes, 1989-09-16 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - New York State Lesbian and Gay Lobby regional Directors, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Orno, 1816-2006: A Bicentennial History by C. Stewart Doty, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Printed images, gay rights related, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Program Book, Dignity, 1981 Convention, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Rochester Gay Task Force letter regarding gay rights, 1977-06-18 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Souvenir Guide, San Diego LGBT Pride, 2011-07-15-2011-07-17 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Workshop Paper, Brother William Roberts, Series #38, 1979-10-27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Questionnaire for John Noble, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - List of Rochester Gay Bars, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Jim’s Bar Information, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Ads, booklets, and flyers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Coalition for Change, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Gay Cable Network Conventions Folder, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Handwritten letter to John Noble from Barbara Schaefer, 1977-07-03 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Handwritten note to John from Bill Derling enclosing Senate-Assembly Regular Sessions, 1989-02-13 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Handwritten notes, long range goals, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Invitation to Empire State Pride Agenda, 1990-11-11 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Letter from East End Gay Organization for Human Rights, Inc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Letter regarding Rochester Lesbian and Gay Political Caucus (RLGPC) and political climate, 1990-12-05 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Letter to Judith Hope regarding Task Force on Domestic Partnership/Civil Union, 2001-11-18 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Letter to NYS Democratic Committee Member regarding Task Force on Domestic Partnership/Civil Union, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Mail Order List for Giovanni’s Room with list of books, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Map directory, Gay Chicago News, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Member Premium Report, Empire Bears, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Memorial poster for Vito Russo, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Monroe Community College, Announcement of Vacancies, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - New York State Democratic Committee, Task Force on Domestic Partnership/Civil Union, Summary Review of Legislative, Legal and Political Issues, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Oscar Wilde Memorial Bookshop, Gay Literature Catalog, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Pamphlet for The Spa at the Grand Resort, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Scanlon, Kevin. “Homosexual rights fighter seeks St. George seat.” Toronto Star., Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Single page from a magazine with ads, 1988-04-26 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - “Homosexual Rights left to states.” Democrat and Chronicle, 1978-05-16 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Administrative Complaint, Statewide Youth Advocacy Project, New York Civil Liberties Union, Action for a Better Community, Inc. vs. School District of the City of Rochester, NY, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Coupon for Roman’s II Health and Recreation Spa, 1980-08-10 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Flier for Voting, list of endorsed candidates, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Flier on Monroe County Human Relations Committee regarding Rochester Task Force requests, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Fort Lauderdale Fun Maps, 2015-2016, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Gay Rights and Conservative Politics, from National review Magazine, 1978-03-17 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Giordano, Mary Ann. “Nab math aide as multiplier in jobless line.”, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - God and the Homosexual Teacher, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Handwritten notes, long range and short range goals, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Health and Social Issues for Bears, Topics for Meetings, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Invitation for fundraising event for the GAGV, 1977-07-01 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Invitation for Holiday Turkey Dinner by Gay Professions Group – R.A.P., 1982-12-05 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Invitation for Rochester Area Professionals benefit for Susan F. Green, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Lambda Legal 2013 Member Report, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Landers, Ann. “Mother hurt by homosexual son advised to seek help for herself.” Democrat and Chronicle, 1978-05-16 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Letter from Reverend Joseph L. Hogan, 1976-02-27 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Letter regarding Catholic Coalition for Gay Civil Rights and registration for Catholic Coalition seminar, 1986-09-02 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Letter regarding support for new human rights legislation, 1977-05-16 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Letter to John Noble from J. Alan Davitt, 1983-04-22 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Letter to staff from Werner H. Kramarsky regarding Affirmative Action Policy, 1977-01 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Maine Civil Liberties Union, 1975-10-17 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Nagourney, Adam and Marcia Kramer. “Assembly kills gay rights bill.”, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - National Gay Task Force, Gay Teachers Support Packet, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - New England (featuring Provincetown, MA) Fun Maps, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Oneida Campground, White Party Weekend, 2002-08-27 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Gays take grievance to the state, Democrat and Chronicle, 1984-06-16 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Pamphlet: Fr. McNeill Speaks, 1976-10-20 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Proposed resolution to the ALC regarding Human Sexuality Task Force, submitted by Lord of Light Lutheran Church, Ann Arbor, Michigan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Respondents to 1978 Employment Survey, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Rochester Gay Men’s Chorus, Spring Concert Program, 1986-05-09 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Sprint Foncard, Attn: Jim Mossgraber, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Statement of support for human and civil rights for homosexual persons by clergy from Rochester and Monroe County, 1977-03-01 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Statement of support for human and civil rights for homosexual persons, 1977-05-12 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Task Force on Sexual Preference, State of Oregon, Department of Human Resources, Preliminary Report, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - The A-Z Guide to LGBT Pride, 2012-06 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - The City Set on a Hill: Reagan, Haig and Human Rights, 1981-03-01 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Flyers, pamphlets, and programs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter and form for support, Human Rights Campaign Fund, 1987-05-29 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter from Dallas Gay Alliance Credit Union, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter from Gay Men’s Health Crisis regarding membership, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter from Scitta Productions, 1997-04-15 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter from the State of New York Executive Department Division of Human Rights regarding Bias-Related Violence and Intimidation Act with questionnaire, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter of Agreement, Gay Rights National Lobby, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter regarding ALA conference, ALA/SRRT, Task Force on Gay Liberation, 1978-12-27 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter regarding enclosed clippings from Governor Cuomo’s Office, 1985-09-26 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter regarding National March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights including flier, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter regarding support statement, Rochester Gay Task Force, 1977-06-18 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter to Friend of RGMC regarding Capacity Building Grant, 2006-10 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter to Wayne H. Steinman, 1985-12-03 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - List of “Friends of the Community”, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - List of “Other possibilities”, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - List of “People to interview”, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - List of contacts, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Lloyd E. Klos Historic Preservation Fund, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Membership List, 2009-06-02 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Membership List, 2009-05-06 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Membership List, 2007-10-03 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Nashoba Activity Log, 2003-11 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Nashoba Board Activity Report, 2003-12-03 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Oneida Camp & Lodge Schedule and Information, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Oneida Campground & Lodge, Tentative Schedule, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Political, 1975-1993
  - Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Rights flier for support, 1992-12 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Determination and Order After Investigation for Case Andrew C. Allocco vs. Monroe County Sheriff’s Department, 1986-12 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Draft Bill to amend penal law with note, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Flier draft for Gary Proud Flier, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Flier for Inauguration, Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1993-01-19 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Flier for reception in honor of Monroe County Legislator John T. Auberger, 1991-04-11 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Information regarding Hardwick case, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Letter regarding initiatives relating to the gay and lesbian community, 1993-01-20 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Letter regarding State University of New York university-wide policy that prohibits discrimination due to sexual orientation, 1982-04-27 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - “Federal Legislation” by James R. Ide, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - “Health Care for the Twenty-First Century Aids,” from Gov. Cuomo’s message to the Legislature, 1986-01-08 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 1986 Legislative Memorandum by New York Civil Liberties Union, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Brochure for Gay Men and Lesbians need Mondale and Ferraro, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - By-Laws National Association of Gay and Lesbian Democratic Clubs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Copies of articles under a cover “1975”, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Domestic Relations Law, S. 928, A. 1146, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Executive Law and Civil Rights Law, S. 1928, A. 2480, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Handwritten letter to Congressperson, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Handwritten letter to Congressperson (Hon. Frank Horton, Hon. Barber Conable), Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Handwritten letter to Javits (Moynihan), Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Handwritten letter to Senator Javits or Moynihan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Letter to New York State Assembly Members regarding Sexual Orientation Bill, 1983-03-10 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Letter to Tim Mains from Alan Heuer with copies of articles and documents attached, 1977-07-14 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - List of Presidential Campaign Contacts by National Association of Gay and Lesbian Democratic Clubs, 1983-03-01 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Membership in the National Association, 1983-03-05 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - New York State Assembly Candidates Poll, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)